Guide to the Social Service Employees Union Photographs PHOTOS 014
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Black and White Photographs, 1952-2002
  - Sub-Series B: Subjects
    - Lower East Side Family Union (LESFU) Fair, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Lower Manhattan Client Line, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Luncheon: Bronx Social Service Commission (SSC) 7th International, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Luncheon: Coward, Leon - Retirement, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Luncheon(s): Homemaker Retirees, 1975-1981 (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Luncheon(s): Homemaker Retirees, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Luncheon(s): Homemaker Retirees, 1984-1984 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Luncheon(s): Homemaker Retirees, 1988-1994 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Luncheon(s): Homemaker Retirees, undated (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Luncheon: Homemakers' Reunion, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Luncheon: New Caseworker Orientation, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Mandela Family Scholarship, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Manhattan Sanitation Workers, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Manhattan SSC Workers Protest, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - March on Washington, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Marches on Washington, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Marches on Washington, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Marches on Washington, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK) Commission, 1983, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - MLK Day Celebrations (Atlanta, New York City), 1988, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - MLK Day Celebrations (Atlanta, Birmingham), 1996, 2001 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - MLK Memorial, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Martinique Hotel, 1981-1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Meany Center for Labor Studies (Silver Springs, Maryland), 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Medical Social Work Division, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Meeting(s): Adult Services and Aging (ASA), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Meeting(s): American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) - Child Welfare, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Meeting(s): Assistant Superintendents of Welfare Promotion Line, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Meeting(s): Bargaining Committee, 1982-1992 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Meeting(s): Black and Puerto Rican Legislative Caucus, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Meeting(s): Board, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Meeting(s): Broadbanding, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Meeting(s): Bureau of Children's' Services (BCS), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Meeting(s): Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW), 1976, 1983-1986, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Meeting(s): BCW, Brooklyn, 1977, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Meeting(s): Case Aides, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Meeting(s): Central Labor Rehabilitation Council, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Meeting(s): Children's Counselors, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Meeting(s): City Council Session, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Meeting(s): Civil Service Abuse Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Meeting(s): Civil Service Committee, 1990-1994 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Meeting(s): Committee on the Homeless, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Meeting(s): Community Service Workers' Chapter, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Meeting(s): Council on Accreditation (COA), 1976 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Meeting(s): Crisis Intervention Services (CIS) Management, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Meeting(s): Delegates' Council, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Meeting(s): Department of Health, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Meeting(s): Division of AIDS Service Subcontracting, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Meeting(s): Dues Committee, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Meeting(s): Ensley, Charles with New York City Council Speaker Peter Vallone at City Hall, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Meeting(s): Executive Committee, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Meeting(s): Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC), 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Meeting(s): HHC Bargaining Committee, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Meeting(s): HHC Chapter, 1978-1984 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Meeting(s): HHC Coalition, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Meeting(s): HHC Old Cost of Living (COLA) Restoration, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Meeting(s): Home Care, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Meeting(s): Houseparents, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Meeting(s): Human Resources Administration (HRA) Chapter, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Meeting(s): HRA Reorganization, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Meeting(s): HRA Staffing, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Meeting(s): Human Resources Specialist (HRS) Series List, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Meeting(s): Labor Committee Against Apartheid, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management (shelters, training, related issues), 1980s (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, 625 Fulton Street, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, 1274 Bedford Avenue, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Agency for Child Development (ACD), 1972-1977, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Agency for Counseling and Rehabilitation Services, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Asbestos Concerns, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Bronx Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Brooklyn BCW, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Bureau of Children's Services (BCS), 1977-1979, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 58)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, BCW, 1977-1984 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Bureau of Client Fraud Investigations (BCFI), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 60)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Case Aides (CA), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 61)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Chelsea Public Workers' Project (PWP)/OHRVAP, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 62)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Children's Center (CC), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 63)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Chrystie Street, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 64)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Community Development Agency (CDA), 1983 (Box 7, Folder 65)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Department of Corrections, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 66)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Department of Employment (DOE), 1979-1982 (Box 7, Folder 67)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Department of Justice, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 68)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Emergency Assistance Unit (EAU), 1984 (Box 7, Folder 69)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Family and Adult Services (FAS), 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 70)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, General Social Services (GSS), 1978, 1981, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 71)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Group Home Violence, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 72)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, HHC (New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation), 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Homemaker Contract Talks, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Homemakers, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Houseparents, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Housing Development Administration (HDA), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Housing, Preservation and Development (HPD), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, HRA (Human Resources Administration), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, HRA Health and Safety Committee, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Human Resources Technician (HRT), 1987 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Income Maintenance Centers (IM/IMC), 1980s (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Liaison and Adjustments Units, 1979, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Men's Shelters, 1979, 1986, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Office of Payroll Administration (OPA), 1980 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Office of Case Intake and Management (OCIM), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Model Cities, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 87)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Neponsit/Model Cities, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 88)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Police Attendants, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 89)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Promotional Exam, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 90)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Protective Services, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Protective Services Agency (PSA) Field Offices, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 92)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Social Service Centers (SSC), 1980s (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Meeting(s): Labor-Management, Zip Codes, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Meeting(s): Labor Party Advocates, Healthcare Reform, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Meeting(s): Liaison and Adjustment Unites, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 96)
    - Meeting(s): Membership, 1975-1979 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Meeting(s): Membership, 1982-1984, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 98)
    - Meeting(s): Membership, 1990-1995 (Box 7, Folder 99)
    - Meeting(s): Model Cities, 1977, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Meeting(s): Negotiating Committee, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Meeting(s): New Juvenile Justice Agency, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Meeting(s): Office of Staff Development and Training (OSDT), 1984 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Meeting(s): Officers with Commissioner Barbara Sabol, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Meeting(s): On Homeless with Dr. George Verny, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Meeting(s): Organizing Committee for "One Member One Vote" (Charles Ensley chairs), 2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Meeting(s): Plant Management, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Meeting(s): Police Attendants, 1988, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Meeting(s): Political Action Committee (PAC), 1976-1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Meeting(s): PAC, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Meeting(s): PAC/Delegate Assembly, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Meeting(s): PAC/Income Tax, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Meeting(s): Productivity Committee, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Meeting(s): Reintegration Committee, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Meeting(s): "Save Mott Haven", 1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Meeting(s): Shelter Chapter, 1976, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Meeting(s): Shelters and Institutions Chapter, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Meeting(s): SSE Chapter, 1977-1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Meeting(s): Unidentified, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Meeting(s): Welfare and Educational Fund, 1985, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Meeting(s): Welfare Reform, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Meeting(s): "White Paper", 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Meeting(s): With Chilean Ambassador, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Meeting(s): With HHC President Joseph Hoffman, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Meeting(s): With HRA Administrator Stanley Brezenoff, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Melrose Center Drug Fair, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Municipal Credit Union (MCU) Shareholders' Committee, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Events, 1983, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - National Association of Social Workers (NASW) NY Chapter, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - National Council of Columbia Associations in Civil Service - Press Conference on Italian-American Employment, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - National Labor Leadership Assembly for Peace, undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Negotiations: Disabled, Aged, Blind (DAB), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Negotiations: Human Resource Association (HRA) Staffing, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Neponsit Home, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - New York City Housing Authority (NYCHA) Tenant Patrol, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - New York City Labor Chorus Annual Concert, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - New York City/Staten Island Kinship Workers' Career Day, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - New York Pioneer Club, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Nicaragua Story, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - North Social Service District Office (Bronx), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Nutrition Programs and Health Fairs, 1979-1982 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Office of Case Management (OCM) Workers, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Officers, 1959-1960, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Officers, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Officers and Staff for Unionist Articles, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Operation Green Thumb (Queens), 1993 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Past Presidents: Viani, Pinkett, Rogoff, Knight, Cohen, Hill, Sperling, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Pension Reopener, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Picketing of the NY Post, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Police Department, 1978, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - PAC Events, 1977, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Press Conferences, 1970s (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Press Conferences, 1980s (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Public Employees Organized to Promote Legislative Equality (PEOPLE) Campaign, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Puerto Rican Day Parade, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Puerto Rican Heritage, 1989, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Queens Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW) Child Abuse Presentation, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Queens Child Welfare Workers at York College, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Queens Parent-Child Association, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Queens Special Services for Children (SSC), 1980s (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Queens Youth Day, 1984-1993 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Rally: Anti Ku Klux Klan, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Rally: Citibank, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Rally: Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Workers, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Rally: Free Mumia (Philadelphia), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Rally: Health Care (Albany), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Rally: May Day (Union Square), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Rally: Peace (United Nations), 1988 (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Rally: Privatization (Bronx), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Rally: Privatization (City Hall), 1992 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Rally: Privatization (Jackson Family Residence, Bronx), 1995 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Rally: Pro-Choice (Washington, DC), 1989 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - Rally: Protest City's Doomsday Budget, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Rally: Protest Closing of Hospitals, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Rally: Protest Closing of Sydenham and Metropolitan Hospitals, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Rally: Seniors/Labor, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Rally: "Settle Our Contract" (City Hall), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - Rally: "Stop Cuts", 1969 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Rally: Support Greyhound Bus Drivers, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 79)
    - Rally: Workers' Memorial Day, 1990-1995 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Regional Manpower #1 Doll Show, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 81)
    - Reisel Show Taping, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Reynolds, Bertha Capen Society, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Riker's Island Substance Abuse Intervention Division, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Runners and other sport competitions, 1978-1992 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - St. Nicholas Center, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - Sanitation Workers, 1979, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 87)
    - Scholarships, 1979, 1986-1996 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Seniors/Senior Centers, 1964, 1984-1994 (Box 8, Folder 89)
    - Shelter: Atlantic Avenue, 1975, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Shelter: Bellevue Men's (special needs), 1990 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Shelter: Brooklyn Arms, 1985, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Shelter: Camp LaGuardia, 1983-1987 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Shelter: Catherine Street, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Shelter: Flushing, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Shelter: Fort Washington, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 96)
    - Shelter: Jackson Avenue Family, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Shelter: Men's, East Third Street, 1980-1986 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Shelter: Men's, Franklin Avenue, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Shelter: Women's, Lafayette and Jones, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 100)
    - Shelter: Women's, Lexington Avenue, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Shelter Workers' Survey, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 102)
    - Signing of the Human Resources Administration (HRA) Contract, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Social Work Month, 1984, 1989, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Social Work Month, 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - SSEU Officers (pre-merger), Martin Morgenstern, President, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - South Africa/Nelson Mandela, 1988, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - South America (Chile), Central America (Nicaragua), Cuba, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Special Services for Children (SSC) Budget Hearings, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - SSC Group Home Drama Production, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - State Case Review and Audit Staff, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Staten Island Bureau of Child Welfare (BCW) Staff and Fire Remains, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Staten Island Child Welfare Agency (CWA), Richmond County Courthouse, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Strike by California United Farm Workers – SSEU support for, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Strike against: Daily News – SSEU support for, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Strike by Detroit Newspaper Workers– SSEU support for, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Strike by District 65 Legal Workers– SSEU support for, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Strike by Eastern Airlines– SSEU support for, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Strike by Frontier Hotel (Las Vegas) – SSEU support for, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Strike by Greyhound– SSEU support for, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Strike by Health and Hospitals Corporation (HHC) – SSEU support for, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Strike by Hotel and Restaurant Employees (H.E.R.E.) Local 11 (Los Angeles) – SSEU support for, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1965: Pre-Strike Picketing, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1965: 20th Anniversary, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1967: Pre-Strike Meeting and Picketing, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1967: 8x10 photographs, January (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1967: 8x10 photographs, May Rally (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1967: 8x10 photographs, August (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1967: 5x7 photographs (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1967: snapshots (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1967: Post-Strike Contract Signing with Judy Mage for SSEU and Marty Morgenstern for Local 371 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Strike/Welfare, 1967: [Post-Strike?] "SSEU Alert", undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Substance Abuse Intervention Division Recognition Day, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Summer Youth Program, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Times Square Hotel, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Training: Civil Service Exam Prep, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Training: Health and Safety, 1981, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Training: New Caseworkers/Members, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Training: Tax Course, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Tucher, Mattie: Recognition Banquet, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - 25th Anniversary of Killing of Civil Rights Workers Chaney, Goodman and Schwerner, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Union Orientation Sessions, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Union Slide Show (original pictures with partial script), [1990?] (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Union Sponsored Legislative Breakfast for City Council Members, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - USSR Trip, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Unity Day, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Voter Registration, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - "Water and Rice" campaign, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Waverly Intake and Management (IM) Center Elevator Crash, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - WBAI Radio Talk Show, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Welfare/Educational Committee, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Welfare Fund Trustees, 1987, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Welfare Local 371 Negotiating Committee, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Williamsburg Income Maintenance Center, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Women's Committee (HRA), 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Women's Committee (SSEU Local 371), 1992, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Woodhull Hospital Tour, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Work Action: Clerical Staff, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Work Action: Harlem Hospital, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Work-In: Bronx BCW, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Workshop: Collective Bargaining, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    - Workshop: Housing Preservation and Development, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Yorkville Center, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Youth Coordinators, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 64)
    - Youth Day: Bryant Park, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 65)
    - Youth Services, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 66)
    - Youth Workers' Graduation, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Series II: Black and White Contact Sheets, 1960-2002
  - Sub-Series A: With Corresponding Negatives Separated
    - Sheets # 1106-1198, 1975-1977 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Sheets # 1200-1277, 1977-May 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Sheets # 1278-1333, May 1978-Dec 1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Sheets # 1335-1391, Jan 1979-Jun 1979 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Sheets # 1392A-1444, Jul 1979-Dec 1979 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Sheets # 1445-1489D, Jan 1980-Jul 1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Sheets # 1490A-1524, Aug 1980-Dec 1980 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Sheets # 1587-1591, Dec 1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Sheets: Unnumbered, labeled "Charles Ensley", Aug 1982 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Unnumbered, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Unnumbered, Mid-1990s (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Unnumbered, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Unnumbered, 1998-2002 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series B: With No Corresponding Negatives
    - Unnumbered, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Unnumbered, 1960s (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Unnumbered, 1970s (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Unnumbered, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Unnumbered, Jan 1981-Jun 1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Unnumbered, Jul 1981-Dec 1981 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Unnumbered, Jan 1982-Aug 1982 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Unnumbered, Sep 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Unnumbered, Jan 1983-Jun 1983 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Unnumbered, Jul 1983-Dec 1983 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Unnumbered, Jan 1984-Jun 1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Unnumbered, Jul 1984-Dec 1984 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Unnumbered, Feb 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Unnumbered, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Unnumbered, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Unnumbered, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Unnumbered, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Unnumbered, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Unnumbered, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Unnumbered, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Unnumbered, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Unnumbered, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Unnumbered, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Unnumbered, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Unnumbered, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Series III: Color Photographs, 1991-2005
  - Subseries A: Snapshots
    - African-American Parade, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - African-American Parade (Corresponding negatives for these images, including Advantix negatives cassette # 538-510 may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color), 2002 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - African-American Parade, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Asbestos Removal (Waverly), 2004 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Bargaining: City-Wide (Corresponding negatives for these images, on Advantix cassette # 766-424, may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color), Jul 26, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Bargaining: Collective, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Bargaining: Collective (Corresponding negatives for these images, on Advantix cassette # 747-361, may be found in Series IV: Negatives, Subseries B: Color), Mar 8, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Bargaining: Collective, Nov 7, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Bargaining: Collective, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 24)